# Jamie Henry



sevenjrh@brighthouse.com



3215765440



linkedin.com/in/jamie-henry-8ba765154



https://jayhenry07.github.io/

## Summary

I am a competitive, and versatile graduate in Computer Engineering from the University of Central Florida. I have a passion for computers, technology, video games and I enjoy problem solving and analyzing algorithms. I have experience in Unity and multiple programming languages, such as the skills listed on my profile.

## **Experience**



#### Server

Olive Garden Sep 2021 - Apr 2022 (8 months)



#### Server

Feb 2016 - Sep 2021 (5 years 8 months)

#### **Education**



### University of Central Florida

Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering Aug 2019 - May 2022



#### Lake-Sumter State College

Associate's degree, General Studies Aug 2017 - May 2019

## **Licenses & Certifications**



Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp



JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp

#### **Skills**

Multitasking • Computer Engineering • Problem Solving • C (Programming Language) • Java • C# • Python (Programming Language) • Data Structures • Time Management • Critical Thinking

#### **Honors & Awards**



## Mathematics Award - Lake-Sumter State College

For academic excellence and achievement in mathematics.